

Mateusz Fonfara

Full Stack Developer

My passion is creating tools for other people to make their life easier. I have experience with each stage of creating applications, from its concept, by the design and architecture planning to final execution and deployment.

I run a blog on medium.com where I share my thoughts on the IT world and contribute to open source.

CONTACT

664 370 447

mateusz.fonfara96@gmail.com

lława, Wyczółkowskiego 16,

matii96.github.io

SKILLS

- Vue.js
- Angular
- Node.js / Nest.js
- Python
- PostgreSQL / MySQL
- Software Architecture

LANGUAGES

English B2 (FCE exam)

INTERESTS

- History
- Swimming

WORK HISTORY

2018-06 - Software Architect, Full Stack Developer Current ITM Software House, Olsztyn, Warmińsko-mazurskie

- Applied established development methodologies such as microservices and event sourcing to architecture design.
- Designed unified authorization system for all web and mobile applications
- Created migration strategies to bridge development gaps between existing software architecture and future updates.

2018-02 - Back End Developer2018-06 NETTOM, Olsztyn, Warmińsko-mazurskie (internship)

- Built databases and table structures for web applications.
- Used php symfony to build projects.

EDUCATION

2019-02 - Master of Science: Information Technology2021-03 University of Warmia And Mazury - Olsztyn

◆ Thesis: Soldier support system

2018-02 - Bachelor of Science: Information Technology2018-06 University of Warmia And Mazury - Olsztyn

Thesis: Chatbot - virtual guide

- Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych w celu rekrutacji zgodnie z art. 6 ust. 1 lit. a Rozporządzenia Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (ogólne rozporządzenie o ochronie danych).
- I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).